voipreview.org 2007-12-18

# Voip Review Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

 **Information Collection and Use** Voip Review is the owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others except when necessary or requested by users such as is the case with our 'Get Quote' form. 

**Log Files** We use IP addresses to administer the site, track user movement and gather demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to identifiable information.

**Sharing** We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**Links** Voip Review contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. Read the privacy statements of each website that collects identifiable information.

**Security** Voip Review takes every precaution to protect users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and offline. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or Social Security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry-SSL. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also protect user information offline. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information** If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as a ZIP code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data.

**Choice/Opt-out** Our users are given the opportunity to opt out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information.
